

# Ali Haj-kanameh

Nationality: Romanian

**(**+40) 734710907

**Date of birth:** 11/01/1997

**Gender:** Male

**Email address:** ali.kanameh@gmail.com

**Website:** <a href="http://akaname.pythonanywhere.com/">http://akaname.pythonanywhere.com/</a>

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ali-haj-kanameh-4244a51a3/

**Oportfolio:** : <a href="http://akaname.pythonanywhere.com/">http://akaname.pythonanywhere.com/</a>

**9 GitHub:**: https://github.com/Alikaname

• Address: Bucharest (Romania)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I dedicated the past year to learn the ins and outs of the IT sector by learning Python programming and Cisco networking to Microsoft servers and Adobe Photoshop to put my newfound skills to further develop myself and others in a productive manner. Having worked in Sales I am familiar with a fast-paced environment and keeping tight deadlines.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Volunteer Management Volunteer**

**UEFA Corporation** [ 04/2021 – 07/2021 ]

**City:** Bucharest **Country:** Romania

- Work Directly with UEFA Management Staff to ensure all tasks are completed smoothly and timely in order to have an excellent experience for both visitors and everyone else;
- Ensure all volunteers arrive on time for their shifts, clock in, and have received their meals for the day;
- Distribute and hand out uniforms for current and newly signed up volunteers;
- Coordinate volunteers to their right positions at the start of their shifts and make sure they know how to do the task at hand;
- Fill in positions for various departments that are low on volunteers.

# **Junior Python Devolper**

**Portal2business** [ 04/2019 - 09/2020 ]

**City:** Bucharest **Country:** Romania

- Collaboration with Hyperion Insurance Group a leading independent, international insurance group based in London;
- Developing their back-end systems and APIs using Python programming language;
- Improved my personal object-orientated development skills in Python;
- Going the extra mile to ensure project deadlines are met in a timely and professional manner.

#### **Sales Assistant**

**To The Top** [ 07/2018 - 11/2018 ]

**City:** Bucharest **Country:** Romania

- Selling products and services using solid arguments to prospective customers;
- Performing cost-benefit analyses of existing and potential customers;
- Maintaining positive business relationships to ensure future sales.

# **Financial Accounting Manager**

**SRN Capital Solutions** [ 02/2018 – 06/2018 ]

**City:** Bucharest **Country:** Romania

- Contact potential or existing customers to inform them about a product or service using scripts;
- Answer questions about products or the company;
- Go the "extra mile" to meet sales guotas and facilitate future sales.

# **Head Account Manager**

**FTW Marketing** [ 07/2017 - 02/2018 ]

**City:** Bucharest **Country:** Romania

- Improve and polish my sales skills by working with clients from all songs of life;
- Opportunity to prove my leadership skills by managing a small team;
- Handle grievances to preserve the company's reputation;
- Keep records of calls and sales and note useful information;
- Ask questions to understand customer requirements and close sales.

# **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

# **Computer Programming**

Zero to Mastery Academy [ 08/2020 - Current ]

## https://zerotomastery.io/

**Field(s) of study:** Information and Communication Technologies : *Information and Communication Technologies (ICTs) not further defined Software and applications development and analysis Database and network design and administration Computer use Information and communication technologies not elsewhere classified* 

Completed Udemy Courses in programming taught by industry veteran Andrei Neagoie:

- Udemy Python Zero to Mastery course taught by
- Udemy Complete Machine Learning and Data Science Zero to Mastery
- Udemy Learning to Learn Efficient Learning Zero to Mastery
- Udemy Master the Coding Interview Data Structures+ Algorithms
- Udemy Complete SQL+Databases.Bootcamp.Zero to Mastery 2020 (in progress)
- Udemy The Complete Web Developer in 2021 Zero to Mastery (in progress)

# **Network Administrator**

**Academia Credis** [ 02/2019 - 02/2020 ]

Address: Bucharest (Romania) https://www.academiacredis.ro/

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies: Database and network design and

administration

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/07838724-b568-459b-a2a9-96fd06a91f1e/linked in profile

Partook in an after-hours Network Administration course with lectures taught by industry veterans in:

- Microsoft Server Manager
- Linux Basic
- Cisco CCNA Routing and switching 1-4

And obtaining my CCNA Certification.

# **Bachelor's degree, Marketing**

**Bucharest Academy of Economic Studies** [ 2014 – 2017 ]

Address: (Romania)

# **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s):

Romanian, Arabic

Other language(s):

#### **English** Spanish

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1 LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1 SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

#### German

LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING A2

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2** 

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Microsoft Office / Microsoft Powerpoint / Zoom / Google Docs / Good listener and communicator / Organizational and planning skills / Team-work oriented / Google Drive

#### IT skills

Network interconnection (Cisco, Switch, Router) / Operating Systems (Windows, Linux) / IT & Networking / Gi tHub / Gitlab Firebase / Google colab

### **Programming skills**

HTML5/CSS, Javascript / Front End Developer / Familiarity with scikit-learn, TensorFlow Machine Learning libraries / JavaScript/jQuery / Master in Python / BootStrap3 / Node js (express framework) / Linux KALI penetration testing

# **DRIVING LICENCE**

Driving Licence: AM
Driving Licence: B1
Driving Licence: B

# **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

CCNA Certification CISCO [ 24/02/2020 ] My CISCO Certificate

# **MANAGEMENT AND LEADERSHIP SKILLS**

#### **Management**

- Started humbly by leading a small team of people through training and advice to help improve their career and workflow;
- Received a once in a lifetime opportunity to work directly with UEFA Management Staff at the EURO 2020 CUP to help improve and sharpen my managerial skills by helping, leading, commanding, and instructing over 850 volunteers that were present for the event along with the rest of the Volunteer Management team.

#### **COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS**

#### **Communication and Debate Skills**

- Commanding skills obtained through the managerial position where I lead my own team and ensured that they understood the task at hand and how to complete it within the target deadline;
- Learned communication by speaking with an international audience from all songs of life at previous sales positions held, which helped me understand and better communicate with people from various backgrounds cultures, and ethnicities;
- Provide solid arguments for clients that best suit their needs and show how a certain product or service can help improve their business or personal life.

#### **VOLUNTEERING**

# **Ceremony Volunteer for Romanian Football Federation**

[ Bucharest, 10/07/2021 - 10/07/2021 ]

Volunteered as a ceremony maker for the Romanian Super Cup Final held at National Arena in Bucharest.

# Volunteer Driver For the Final Draw EURO 2020 event held in Bucharest by UEFA

[ Bucharest, 11/2019 - 12/2019 ]

Volunteer, working with the International UEFA team to help transport VIPs for the Bucharest Final Draw event for EURO 2020 in December 2019 at ROMEXPO.